http://www.geometrica.com/en/privacy-policy

Calendario de Eventos
Privacy Policy  This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?When filling and sending the Inquiry Form on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.When do we collect information?We collect information from you when you fill out the Inquiry Form.How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you fill out the Inquiry Form to send periodic emails (newsletters via iContact) regarding our products and services, and to answer any specific requests that you may have posed. Your information is not transferred to any other party in the US or abroad.How do we protect your information?We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards. We do not use an SSL certificate. We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to: Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It will not affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.Third-party disclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.Third-party linksWe do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.California Online Privacy Protection ActCalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpufAccording to CalOPPA, we agree to the following: Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.You can change your personal information by emailing us.How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?We do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13.Fair Information PracticesThe Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify you via email within 7 business days.We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which states that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.CAN-SPAM ActThe CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.We collect your email address in order to:Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM Act, we agree to the following:Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (effective May 25, 2018)This Privacy Policy complies with the applicable requirements of the GDPR.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, or if you want to obtain a copy of your personal information held by Geometrica, you may contact us using the information below.Attention: Privacy Policy ManagementGeometrica, Inc.12300 Dundee Ct., Ste. 200, Cypress, TX 77429, USAprivacypolicymanager@geometrica.com
